A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1 FA078
Rockefeller Archive Center
Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1
1953-1980
Rockefeller Archive Center
Agricultural Development Council
FA078
47.17 Cubic Feet 122 document boxes.
Arrangement note
This collection is arranged in five series:
Series 1 - General Series 2 - American Universities Research Program Series 3 - Research and Training Network Series 4 - Training Materials Project Series 5 - Agricultural Development Council Annual Reports Series 1032 - Photographs
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 3B 01
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted are noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains meeting minutes, personnel files, grant information, printed material, and photographs.
Agricultural education; Education; Philanthropy; Agriculture; Asia; Public welfare; Developing countries; Social sciences
- General, 1953-1977; 1
  Arrangement note
  Series 1 is arranged in 7 subseries:
  Subseries A - Office Files Subseries 1 - Board of Trustees Subseries 2 - Conferences Subseries 3 - Book and Equipment Grants Subseries 4 - Personnel Subseries 5 - Publications Subseries 6 - Reading File
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes minutes of the Board of Trustees, conferences sponsored by the ADC, book and equipment grants, personnel files, publications, and reading files.
  - General - Office Files, 1.A
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    - Budget, 1954-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted material.
    - Visiting Professors - Taichung, China (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General - Board of Trustees, 1.1
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - Incorporation Certificate and By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1953-May 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, October 1955-June 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, June 1956-June 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, September 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, January 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, October 1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, January 1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, June 1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, October 1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, January 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, June 1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, September 1960 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, January-April 1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, June 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, September 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, June 1962 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, September 1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Agenda and Minutes, January 8, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Agenda, January 12, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, January 12, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Agenda, Minutes, Interim Actions, September-December 1963 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Agenda, Minutes, Interim Actions, January-April 1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Agenda, Minutes, Interim Actions, June 17-25, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Agenda and Minutes, November 4, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Agenda, Minutes, Interim Actions, January-March 1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Agenda, Minutes, June 1965-October 1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Agenda and Minutes, January 24, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Agenda and Minutes, June 12, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Agenda and Minutes, January 16, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Agenda and Minutes, June 26, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Agenda and Minutes, January 14, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Agenda and Minutes, July 13, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - General - Conferences, 1.2
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists Grantees, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists Grantees, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Economics Teaching in Southeast Asia, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Related Archival Materials note
      Photographs.
    - Agricultural Economics Teaching in Southeast Asia, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Training - New York, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Training Asian Graduate Students in Agricultural Economics, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Training Asian Graduate Students in Agricultural Economics, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Training - Urbana, Illinois, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Training - Urbana, Illinois, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bicol Seminar - Agricultural Planning, 1965 (Box 1A, Folder 1)
      See also Box 2, Folder 13. Photographs.
    - Economics of Agricultural Development, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Training - Amherst, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Training - Amherst, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bicol Seminar - Agricultural Planning, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      See also Box 1A, Folder 1. Photographs.
    - Graduate Training - Johns Hopkins University, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Training - Johns Hopkins University - Reports, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Training - Rockefeller University, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Training - Rockefeller University - Reports, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Staff Conferences - Bandung, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Staff Conferences - Bandung, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Staff Conferences - Bandung, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Staff Conferences - Penang, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Staff Conferences - Bangkok, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Staff Conferences - Bangkok, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Staff Conferences - Manila, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Staff Conferences - Manila, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Staff Conferences - New Delhi, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Staff Conferences - New York, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Staff Conferences - Manila, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Staff Conferences - Singapore, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Staff Conferences - Hong Kong, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Staff Conferences - Bali, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Staff Conferences - Nepal, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - General - Book and Equipment Grants, 1.3
    - Afghanistan - Rural Development Department - Pamir Park, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Book Grant
    - Agricultural Cooperative College - Korea, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Economics Society - India, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Agricultural Sciences - Bangalore, India, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute, 1956-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Andalas - Indonesia, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Anhamali University - Madras, India, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Balwant Rajput College - Agra, India, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bicol Development Planning Board, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - University of Bombay, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brawidjaja University, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Central Luzon State University, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Central Philippine University, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - University of Ceylon, 1956-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - University of Ceylon, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Equipment Grant
    - China Research Institute of Land Economics, 1955-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chinju Agricultural College - Korea, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chinju Agricultural College, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Christian College of Dairy Agriculture - Japan, 1957, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Chulalongkorn University, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Coimbatore Agriculture College - India, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - College of Agriculture - Poona, India, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - College of Agriculture - Malaya, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Cornell University, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - University of Dacca, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - University of Dacca, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Damodar Valley Corporation, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Delhi School of Economics, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - East Pakistan Agricultural University, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Farm Management Research Center - India, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of India, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Fu-min Geographical Institute of Economic Development, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Gadjah Mada University, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Gadjah Mada University, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Gokhale Institute of Politics and Economics, 1961-1965 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Government Agricultural College - India, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Herbal Agricultural College, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Hokkaido University, 1955-1964 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Hokkaido University, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Indian Agricultural Research Institute, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Indian Central Jute Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Indian School of Political Economy, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Indonesia, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - University of Indonesia, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - University of Indonesia - Faculty of Economics, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Institute of Agriculture - Anand, India, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - International Cultural Center - New Delhi, India, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Kagoshima University, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Kanpur Agricultural Library - India, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Kasetsart University, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Kasetsart University, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Kasetsart University - Rural Education Department, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - University of Kerala - India - Economics Department, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Khan, Mahmood Ali, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Khon Kaen University - Thailand, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Kiyosato Educational Experimental Project, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Korea - Ministry of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Kyoto University, 1955-1958, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Kyoto University, 1954-1965 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Kyushu University, 1955-1957, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Kyushu University, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Universitas Lambung Mangkurat - Indonesia, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Lee, Pil Kyu, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - University of Madras, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Malaya - Ministry of Agriculture, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - University of Malaya, 1956-1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - University of Malaya, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Malaya Federal Land Development Authority, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Mindanao State University, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Mountain Agricultural College, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Muda Agricultural Development Authority - Malaysia, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Nagpur Agriculture College - India, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Nair, Kusum, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - National Agricultural Cooperatives Federation, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - National Research Institute of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - National Research Institute of Agriculture, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - National Taiwan University, 1956-1963 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - National Taiwan University, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Nepal, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Nishimura, Hiroyuki, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - University of North Sumatra, 1959-1969 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Notre Dame of Jolo College - Philippines, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Obihiro Zootechnical University, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Padjadjaran State University, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - University of Peshawar, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Philippines, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - University of the Philippines, 1955-1966 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - University of the Philippines, 1954-1955, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - University of the Philippines - Institute of Asian Studies, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Punjab Agricultural College, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - University of Rajasthan, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Royal Irrigation Department - Thailand, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Saint Louis University - Philippines, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - University of San Carlos, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - School of Agriculture for Boys - Peradeniya, Ceylong, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Seoul National University, 1957-1958, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Seoul National University - College of Agriculture, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Shiga Agricultural College, 1955-1960 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Shiga Agricultural College, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Silliman University, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Silliman University, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Silliman University - Cultural Research Center, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - University of Singapore, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Universitas Sjiah Kuala, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Soeharjo, A., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Srinivasan, M., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Taiwan Provincial Chung Hsing University, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Taiwan Provincial College of Agriculture, 1955-1967 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Takahaski, I., 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Tamil Nadu Agricultural University, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Thailand, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Tohoku National Agricultural Experiment Station, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Tokyo University, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Tottori University, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Tottori University, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Visva Bharati, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Visva Bharati, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Wallace, Robert, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - West Pakaistan Agricultural University, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Weitzner, Janet, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Wharton, Clifton Jr., 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Wong, Marjorie, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Xavier University - Philippines, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - General - Personnel, 1.4
    Permanently restricted - Confidential Material.
    - Allee, Ralph H. - Biography, Reports, Correspondence, Expenses (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Allee, Ralph H. - General (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allee, Ralph H. - Retirement Benefits (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Barnett, Milton - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Barnett, Milton - Salary (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Barnett, Milton - Biography, Employment Terms, Sabbatical, Travel (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Barnett, Milton - Finances (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Barnett, Milton - Reports (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Beers, Howard W., 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Beers, Howard W., 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Beers, Howard W., 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Beers, Howard W., 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bloodgood, Phyllis A. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Borton, Raymond - Biography, Correspondence, Employment Terms, Finances (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Borton, Raymond - Retirement, Travel, University Appointment (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Brown, David W. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Chacona, Sapfo (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Cherrybone, Edith Ann (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Diamant, Julia (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Dickerson, Russell B. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Fort, Raymond E. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Fox, Robert (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Gittinger, J. Price II, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Gittinger, J. Price II, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Green, Donald G. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Hrabovszky, John P. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Kearl, Bryant - Biography, Employment Terms, Finances (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Kearl, Bryant - Reports, Benefits, Travel (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Lackner, Delores (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Lewis, A. B. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Locke, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Metz, Maida (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Moseman, Albert - Biography, Correspondence, Employment Terms, Finances (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Moseman, Albert - Reports (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Moseman, Albert - Benefits, Travel (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Mosher, Arthur - Reports (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Patterson, Barbara (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Penny, David H. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Peterson, Arthur W. (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Ramabhushanam, Gay (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Ruttan, Vernon - Reports (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Schickele, Rainer - Biography, Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Schickele, Rainer - Employment Terms, Reports (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Schickele, Rainer - Finances, Benefits, Travel (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Schochet, Arlene (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Schutjer, Wayne J. (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Sitton, Gordon R. (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Snodgrass, Milton (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Southworth, Herman M. - Biography, Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Southworth, Herman M. - Employment Terms, Finances, Korea Assignment (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Southworth, Herman M. - Reports, Travel (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Stevens, Robert D. (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Stigberg, Elizabeth (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Strout, Alan M. - Biography, Correspondence, Employment Terms (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Strout, Alan M. - Finances (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Strout, Alan M. - Reports, Benefits, University Agreement (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Tersillo, Frances (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Tharrington, Alberta (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Wagner, Melvin M., 1962-1968 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Wagner, Melvin M., 1962-1968 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Ward, Edward H. (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Weaver, Thomas F. - Biography, Correspondence, Employment Terms, Finances (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Weaver, Thomas F. - Benefits, Reports, Travel (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Wharton, Clifton R. - Biography, Correspondence, Employment Terms (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Wharton, Clifton R. - Finances, Reports, Travel (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - General - Publications, 1.5
    - Announcements (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1953-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1953-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1953-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1953-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Avard Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Books and Monographs (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Borton, Raymond E. (edit.), Case Studies to accompany Getting Agriculture Moving. NY. 1967.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Borton, Raymond E. (edit.) Selected Readings to accompany Getting Agriculture Moving. Volume I. NY. 1972.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Borton, Raymond E. (edit.) Selected Readings to accompany Getting Agriculture Moving. Volume II. NY. 1972.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Boyce, James K. and Robert E. Evenson. Agricultural Research & Extension Program. NY. 1975.
      Buitron, Anibal. How Progress Came to Huagrapampa. An Experiment in Community Development. NY. 1966.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Chan, Francis and William Collier, Ir. Koestono, Encik Rahmat Suffian, Encik Ti Teow Choo. Seminar on Income Improvement Programs for Smallholders. A Report of a Traveling Seminar in Indonesia, Thailand and Malaysia, May 12-27, 1973. Singapore.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Committee on Economics Teaching Material for Asian Universities (edit.) Economic Theory and Practice in the Asian Setting. Volume I - Macroeconomics; Volume II - Microeconomics. New Delhi. 1976.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Committee on Economics Teaching Material for Asian Universities (edit.) Economic Theory and Practice in the Asian Setting. Volume III - The Economics of Agriculture; Volume IV - The Economics of Development. New Delhi. 1976.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Eicher, Carl K. Research on Agricultural Development in Five English-Speaking Countries in West Africa. NY. 1970.
      Foster, Phillips W. Research on Agricultural Development in North Africa. NY. 1967.
      Holmes, Horace C. No Pone Valley. NY. 1967.
      International Rice Research Institute. Bibliography on Socio-Economic Aspects on Asian Irrigation. Singapore. 1976.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Kearl, Bryant. (edit.) Field Data Collection in the Social Sciences: Experiences in Africa and the Middle East. NY. 1976.
      Lombardo, Heraclio A. Research On Agricultural Development in Central America. NY. 1969.
      McLoughlin, Peter F.M. Research On Agricultural Development in East Africa. NY. 1967.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Moseman, Albert H. Building Agricultural Research System in the Developing Nations. NY. 1970.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Moseman, Albert H. (edit.) National Agricultural Research Systems in Asia. NY. 1971.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Mosher, A.T. Creating A Progressive Rural Structure. To Serve a Modern Agriculture. NY. 1969.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Mosher, A.T. Getting Agriculture Moving. Essentials for Development and Modernization. NY. 1966.
      Mosher, A.T. Resume of Rural Development Experience. NY. 1977.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Mosher, A.T. Training Manual for group study of Getting Agriculture Moving. NY. 1966.
      Mosher, A.T. Serving Agriculture as an Administrator. NY. 1975.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Mosher, Arthur T. Thinking About Rural Development. NY. 1976.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Mosher, A.T. To Create a Modern Agriculture. Organization and Planning. NY. 1971.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 4, Folder 23)
      National Seminar Report No. 5. Irrigated Agriculture in Northern Thailand, March 17-19, 1974.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Schertz, L.P. and A.R. Stevenson, A.M. Weisblat. (edits.) International Training in Agricultural Economic Development. NY. 1976.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Schuh, G. Edward. Research On Agricultural Development in Brazil. NY. 1970.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Southworth, Herman (edit.) Farm Mechanization in East Asia. Singapore. 1972.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Southworth, Herman (edit.) Some Studies of Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Marketing in Asia. Singapore. 1974.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 5, Folder 28)